Guide to the New Dimensions Media records M1577
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Accession 2008-144
  - Sub-Series 1: Biographical information of interviewees
    - Holden, Larry, 1988-1989 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Holland, Gail Bernice, 1998-1999 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Hollander, Lorin, 1978-1992 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Holmer, Jana (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Holt II, Lindsay, 1988-1997 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Holt, Lorri, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      2351 and unspecified
    - Homolka, Ayisha, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Hooper, Dick (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Hopkins, Patricia and Sherry Anderson, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Hoppe, Stephanie, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Horn, Frances, 1977-1988 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Horn, Paul, 1977-2006 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Houston, Jean, 1984-2006 (Box 72, Folder 1-4)
      2416, 2523, 2560, 2562, 2567, 2658, 2819, 2968
    - Hovhaness, Alan, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Howard, Vernon, 1980-1996 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Huang, Chungliang Al, 1984-2003 (Box 72, Folder 7-8)
      2739, 2787
    - Hubbard, Barbara, 1979-2007 (Box 73, Folder 1-4)
      2419, 3206
    - Hubbard, L. Ron, 1986-1987 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Huddleston, Peggy, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      2621
    - Huffines, Launa, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Huffington, Arianna, 1994-2001 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Hughes, K. Wind (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Hulse-Stephens, David, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Hunt, Michele, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      2705
    - Hunter, Allan, 2008 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      3257
    - Huxley, Laura, 1991-1994 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      2284
    - Hurley, Tom, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      2693
    - Hutner, Jeff, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Huyler, Stephen (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Hwoschinsky, Paul, 1991-1998 (Box 74, Folder 10)
      2229
    - Idarius, Jerri-Jo, 1991-1992 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Illes, Peter, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Illich, Ivan, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Ingerman, Sandra, 1991-2007 (Box 74, Folder 14)
      3202; additional unidentified program number
    - Ingram, Catherine, 1990-2003 (Box 74, Folder 15)
      2987; additional unidentified program number
    - Isaacs, David, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Isaacs, William, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 17)
      2699
    - IsanaMada, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Isenberg, Nancy, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      Unidentified
    - Internation Transpersonal Center (ITC), 1995 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Iyer, Pico, 2008 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      3256
    - Janiger, Oscar M.D., 1993 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      2379
    - Jansma, Gwen, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      2312
    - Jarman, Beth and George Land, 1991-1992 (Box 75, Folder 7-8)
    - Jarrett, Keith, 1982-1997 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Jasmuheen and Mark Comings, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      2863
    - Jaxon-Bear, Eli, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 11)
      2999
    - Jayanti, Amber, 1998-2003 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Jayanti, Sister, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Jayapal, Pramila, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      2873
    - Jay, Suki, 1986-1992 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Jackson, Jessie, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Jackson, Wes, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Jacobs, Joseph, 1993-1994 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Jaeckel, Joan, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      3151
    - Jaffe, Dennis, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - James, Diana, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      2745
    - Jampolsky, Gerald and Diane Cirincione, 1990-2000 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      2203, 2849
    - Jeffers, Susan, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 10)
      2320
    - Jeanloz, Raymond, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Jefferson, Thomas (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Jensen, Derrick, 2004-2006 (Box 76, Folder 13)
      3180
    - Jensen, Robert, 2002-2004 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      3048
    - Jesus, 1999 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Jetsunma, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Jochmans, Joseph, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Johanson, Patricia, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - John-Roger, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Alia, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Rev. Deborah. L., 2007 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      3223
    - Johnson, Doug, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, John L., 1993-1997 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, Robert, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Willard, 1986-1987 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Johnston, Charles, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Jones, Bill T., 1994; 2625 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Jones, David, 1993-1996 (Box 77, Folder 15)
      2426
    - Jones, Dewitt (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Jones, Graeme (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Jones, Hardy, 1976-2001 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Jones, Michael, 1996-1998 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      2633
    - Jones, Ron, 1980-2002 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      1989
    - Jonsson, Bonnie O'Brien, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Jordan, Peg, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Josten, Katherine, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Joy, Brugh, 1980-1996 (Box 78, Folder 8-9)
    - Judith Anodea, 2003-2006 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      3157
    - Jue, Ron, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Jung, Carl, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Juergensmeyer, Mark (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Justice, Blair, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Kabat-Zinn, Jon, 1985-1997 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      2436
    - Kahn, Shabda, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Kain, John, 2007 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      3194, 3197
    - Kaiser, Jon, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      2563
    - Kalchuri, Bhau, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      2782
    - Kalinda, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Kalu Rimpoche (and Lama Lodu), 1982-1998 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Kanya, 1980-1988 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Kapur, J.C., 1982-1995 (Box 79, Folder 10)
      1724
    - Karpinski, Gloria, 1990-2002 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Karunamayi, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 12)
      2585
    - Kasl, Charlotte, 1991-2001 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      2340
    - Kastl, Richard (Box 80, Folder 2)
      1193, 1304
    - Kater, Peter, 1995-1997 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Katie, Byron, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      3047
    - Katz-Wallace, Michael (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Kaufman, Alfred, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Kaufman, Barry, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 7-8)
      2328
    - Kauchik, Dr. R.P., 1978 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Kaye, Les, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      2668
    - Keating, Father Thomas, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Keegan, Peter M.D., 2000 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Keen, Jan, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Keen, Sam, 1991-1997 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      1747, 1805, 1858, 2254
    - Keiser, Linda, 1986-1991 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      Program number unidentified
    - Keleman, Stanley, 1983-1989 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      Program numbers unidentified
    - Kellner-Rogers, Myron (Box 81, Folder 5)
      2653
    - Kelly, Georgia, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Kelly, Marjorie, 2001-2002 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Kemmis, Daniel, 1996 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      Spirit of
    - Kenley, John, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      2949
    - Kennedy, Alexandra, 1991-2002 (Box 81, Folder 10)
      2271, 2629
    - Kennedy, Robert, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Kent, Marty, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Kerns, David, 2007 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      3210
    - Kesey, Ken, 1986-1998 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Keshavadas, Sant, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Kessel, Brent, 2008 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      3262
    - Kessler, Rachel (previous name Shelley Kessler), 2002-2005 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      3088
    - Kessler, Shelley (aka Rachel Kessler), 1990-1992 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      2278
    - Kesten, Deborah, 1995-1998 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      2733
    - Keveles, Melanie and Judith Dubin, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      2200
    - Keyes, Ken, 1980-1986 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Lama Khenpo Konchog Gyaltsen, 1991-1995 (Box 82, Folder 10)
      2306
    - Kielburger, Craig, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Kieschnick, Michael, 2001-2003 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      2984, 2990
    - Taei Yun Kim, 1991-1999 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      2669
    - Kimmel, Jim, 1977-1980 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Kimmey, John, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - King, Larry (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - King, Marilyn, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      299225
    - King, Dr. Martin Luther, Jr., 2001 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Kingsolver, Barbara, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Kingston, Maxine Hong, 1989-1994 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Kircher, Pamela, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 12)
      2584
    - Kivel, Paul, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Kleefeld, Carolyn, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Klein, Allen, 1988-1995 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      2534
    - Kleinmaier, G. W., 1990 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Kleitsch, Sharon Joy, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Klime, Jon, 1987-1995 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Kobaly, Robin and Doug Thomson, 2003-2006 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      3030, 3169
    - Kofalk, Harriet, 1992-1993 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Koff-Chapin, Deborah, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Kogel, Joe, 1985-1990 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Kogi People, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Kohli, Carol, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Kornfield, Jack, 1994-2008 (Box 84, Folder 10)
      2452, 3267
    - Korten, David C., 1996-2006 (Box 84, Folder 11)
      2763, 3145
    - Kortge, Carolyn Scott, 1998-1999 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Kotler, Arnie, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Kramer, Mark, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Kramer, Joel and Diana Alstad, 1980-1995 (Box 84, Folder 15)
      2549
    - Krech, Gregg, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Krippner, Stanley, 1988-1998 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Krishnamurti, U. G., 1989 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Krishnamurti, J., 1982-1994 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      1782, 1865
    - Krohnen, Michael, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      2634
    - Kropf, Richard W., 1990-1998 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Krugman, Paul, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Kriyananda, Sri, 1991-2006 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Kubler-Ross, Elizabeth, 1980-1997 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Kudler, David, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 9)
      3057
    - Kuhn, Maggie, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Kumar, Satish, 1999-2003 (Box 85, Folder 11)
      2770, 3016
    - Kunga Rinpoche, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Kuralt, Charles, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Kurtz, Ron, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Kushi, Michio, 1978-1994 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Labatte, Robert Woableza and Deana Keppel, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - LaBerge, Stephen, 1981-1990 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - LaCerva, Victor, 1998 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - La Chapelle, David, 2001 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - La Chapelle, Dolores, 1991-1997 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Lad, Vasant D., 1993-1996 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - La Duke, Betty, 1983-1998 (Box 86, Folder 6-8)
    - La Duke, Winona, 1990-1998 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      2738
    - Lakritz, Kenneth and Thomas Knoblauch, 2000-2001 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Lakoff, George (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Lambert, Georgia (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - L'Amoreaux, Claudia, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      3027
    - Lamont, Bette, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      3095
    - Landcaster, Brad, -2006 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      3175
    - Landon, Carole, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Lane, John, 2007-2008 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      3254
    - Lanier, Jean, 1990-1993 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      2196
    - Lanman, Cecila, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Lapid-Bogda, Ginger, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 12)
      3094
    - Lappe, Anna, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Lappe, Frances Moore, 1981-2008 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      3248
    - Lapierre, Dominique, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 2)
      2250
    - Larkin, 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Larsen, Stephen and Robin Larsen, 1990-1991 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      2249
    - Laszlo, Ervin, 2007 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      3203
    - Laufer, Joanna and Kenneth Lewis, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Laurance, Arlene (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Lawe, Valerie, 1997 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Lawlor, Robert, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Lawrence, Lisa, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Lawrence, Pat, 1998 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Lawrence-Lightffot, Sara, 1990-1994 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Lazaris, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Lear, Norman, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Leary, Timothy, 1983-1995 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Lee, John, 1991 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Leboyer, Frederick, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Lee, Mun Wah, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Lee, William Pay, 2007 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      3207
    - Leeds, Regina, 2001 (Box 89)
    - Legendre, Bokara (Box 89, Folder 5)
      3063
    - Leger, Barbara, 2003-2008 (Box 89, Folder 6)
      3255
    - Le Guin, Ursula, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Lehman, Andrew, 1997 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Leicester, Sandy, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Leider, Richard, 1981-2000 (Box 89, Folder 10-11)
      2676, 2868
    - Leider, Richard, 1999-2000 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Levoy, Gregg, 1997-1999 (Box 89, Frame 13)
    - Levy, Juliette de Bairacli, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Levy, Steven, 1991-1992 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      2341
    - Lewis, Victor, 1990-1993 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Liberman, Jacob, 1991-1998 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      2843
    - Liedloff, Jean, 1981-1999 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Lietaer, Bernard, 1997-2004 (Box 90, Folder 6-8)
      2702, 2760
    - Light, Cassandra, 1985-1999 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Lilly, John, 1988-1990 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Lillywhite, Mac (DTI), 1992 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Limbaugh, Rush, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Lingo, T.D.A., 1990 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Lipman, Kennard, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Lippe, Toinette, 2002 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      2941
    - Lipton, Bruce, 1991-2005 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      2661, 3093
    - Lithman, Alan, 2000 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      2825
    - Little, Peter, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Liu, Dr. Grace, 1985-1990 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Livingston, Penny, 2003 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Lloyd, Susan Caperna, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Lock, Kevin, 1992-1993 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Lama Lodo, 1988-1992 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Loeb, Paul, 1994-2004 (Box 91, Folder 14-15)
      2505, 2779, 3046
    - Loeffler, Jack, 2003 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Longaker, Christy, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 17)
      2617
    - Lookinghorse, Arvol and Carol Ann Hart, 1991-1993 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Lopez, Barry, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Love, Lisa, 2007 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      3228
    - Lovejoy, Tom, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      3165
    - Lovelock, James, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Lovett-Keen, 1989-1995 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Lowe, Paul, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Lowen, Alexander M.D., 1995 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Lowen, Rajen, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Lowenstein, Janai, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Loye, David, 2002-2007 (Box 92, Folder 10)
      2935, 3230
    - Lozoff, Bo and Sita, 1994-2000 (Box 92, Folder 11)
      2527, 2813
      CD
      Eyes so Soft, Bo Lozoff & Friends live in concer
    - Luce, Gay, 1983-1997 (Box 92, Folder 12-13)
      1767
    - Lub, Sergio, 1992-2000 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Ludeman, Kate, 1988-2003 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Luedde, Mike, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Luhrs, Janet, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Lukensmeyer, Carolyn, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Luks, Allan (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Lund, Laurel, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Luthman, Shirley, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Luyckx, Marc, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Lynch, Dudley and Paul Kordis, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Lynch, Jerry, 1990-1994 (Box 93, Folder 11)
      2434
    - Lynch, Ray, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Lynn, Dianna, 1992-1993 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Lyons, Jerrigrace, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Lyons, Marlena S., 2001 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Maathai, Wangari, 1995-2000 (Box 93, Folder 16)
      2914
      - MacGillis, Miriam Therese, 2003 (Box 93, Folder 17)
      - Mack, John, 1993-1994 (Box 93, Folder 18)
        An unspecified program number
      - Macy, Fran, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Macy, Joanna, 1989-2008 (Box 94, Folder 1-2)
      2198
    - Madson, Patricia Ryan, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      3108
    - Maharaji, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Maharisi, 1988-1993 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Maitland, Arnaud, 2006 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      3138
    - Ma Jaya, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Malkin, Gary, 1999-2005 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      3077
      Includes CD
    - Malone, Dennis and Margaret, 1992 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Marie, Nancy, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Mamas, Michael, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Mandel, Terry, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Mander, Jerry, 1991-1998 (Box 94, Folder 13)
      2297, 2298
    - Mangelsen, Tom, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Manning, Matthew (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Manger, Bruno, 1992 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Mansfield, Vic, 1987-1997 (Box 95, Folder 4-5)
      2615
    - Mapes, Dan, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Marazzi, William, 1992 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Mardis, Linda Keiser, 1994-1996 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Markides, Kyriacos, 1986-1994 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Margulius, Nance, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Markova, Dawna, 1991-2008 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      2610, 2828, 3113, 3249
      Spiriti of the Tiimes
    - Marks, Linda, 1988-1990 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      Program numbeo
      2179
    - Marks, Stephan, 1989-1990 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Marler, Joan, 1989-1995 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Marlin, Alice Tepper, 1988-1995 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Marrin, West, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      3026
    - Marshak, David, 2005-2006 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      3100, 3151
    - Marshall, Laurie, 2002-2003 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      2418
    - Mason, Marilyn, 1993-1995 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Massy, Robert (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Masters-Darling, Kathryn, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Masters, Robert, 1993-1995 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Mathiessen, Peter, 1990-1993 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Mathieu, Allaudin, 1993-1994 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Matthew, Caitlin and John, 1991-1998 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Mattison, Avon, 1990-1997 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Maturana, Humberto, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Maxfield, Mo, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - May, Mitchell, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      P
      2377
    - Mayer, Michael (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Mayer, Steven, 2006 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      3181
    - Maginnes, Darshan, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Mayo, Peg Elliot, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Maysles, Albert, 2007 (Box 97, Folder 11)
      C0010
      Podcast
    - McDonough, William, 1997-2003 (Box 97, Folder 12-13)
      2900, 2901, 2902, 2973, 2988
    - McBride, Jeff, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - McCallister, Joyce, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - McCamant, Kathryn and Charles Durrett, 1983-1990 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - McCarthy, Michael, 1991-1992 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - McCloskey, Caryn Levin, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - McCoy, Harold, 1991-2005 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      2269, 2969
    - McCullough, Donald, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - McDougall, John, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      2330
    - McElroy, Susan Chernak, 1999-2002 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - McFerin, Bobby, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - McIntosh, Steve, 2007 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      3227
    - McGaa, Ed, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 7)
      2353
    - McKay, Noah M. D., 2008 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      3277
    - McKenna, Terence, 1983-1992 (Box 98, Folder 9)
      2268
    - McKeown, Ciarran (Box 98, Folder 10)
      2586
    - McKibben, Bill, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - McKinnon, Judith, 1976-2003 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - McLanaban, Sandra, 1996 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - McLaren, Brian, 2005 (Box 98, Folder 14)
      Unknown
    - McLaughlin, Corinne and Gordon Davidson, 1994-1995 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      2488
    - McManus, Philip, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - MacMichael, Lynn, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - McNiff, Shawn, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      2555
    - Meade, Michael, 1990-2008 (Box 99, Folder 5-6)
      2243, 2393, 3211, 3243
    - Means, Russell, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      2546
    - Meeker, Joe, 1983-1997 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Meera, Mother (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Meggyesy, David and George Pegalow, 1987-1988 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Mehdi, Sharon, 2006 (Box 99, Folder 11)
      3147
    - Mehl-Madrona, Lewis, 1988-1990 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Melucci, Albert, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Hunbatz Men, 1989-1990 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Menchu Tum, Rogoberta, 1992-1999 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Menkin, Dan, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Merkel, Jim, 2005 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Mesher, Alan, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Metz, Katherine, 1992 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      2305
    - Metzger, Deena, 1989-2002 (Box 100, Folder 3-4)
      2356
    - Metger, Joel (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Metzner, Ralph, 1989-2000 (Box 100, Folder 6-7)
    - Meyers, Robin, 2006 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Michael, Pamela, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Milburn, Judith Annette, 1990-1994 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Miles, Richard, 1986 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Miller, Alice, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Miller, Emmett, R., M. D., 1979-2008 (Box 101, Folder 2-3)
      2595, 2694
    - Miler, Jacqueline, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Miller, Joe, 1986-1993 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Miller, D. Patrick, 1988-1998 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Miller, Radhika, 1990-1994 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Miller, Ron, 2005 (Box 101, Folder 8)
      3091
    - Miller, Sukie, 1997 (Box 101, Folder 9)
      2670
    - Miller, William, 1986-1987 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Millman, Dan, 1984-1995 (Box 101, Folder 11-12)
      2530
    - Mills, Stephanie, 1989-1998 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Milton, John, 1989 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Mindell, Arnold and Amy Mindell, 1989-2002 (Box 102, Folder 3-5)
      1957, 2318, 2325
      An unnunbered program series
    - Mingyer, Rinpoche Yongey, 2007 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      Prog
      3201
    - Mini, John, 1998 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Mipham, Sakyong, 2003 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      Pr
      2970
    - Mirabal, Robert, 2004 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Mishlove, Jeffrey, 1973-1997 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Mishra Ramamurti, 1975 (Half-box 103, Folder 1)
    - Mitchell, Edgar, 2005 (Half-box 103, Folder 2)
    - Mitchell, Howie, 1986-1991 (Half-box 103, Folder 3)
    - Mitchell, Stephen, 1988 (Half-box 103, Folder 4)
      2714
    - Mizzi, Fr., 1998 (Half-box 103, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 2: Subject files, 2
    - AA Press packages (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Addiction (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Adobe font catalog (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Advertising (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - African-American (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Aging (Box 104, Folder 6)
      Includes two cassette tapes, one of UCF "Spiritual Eldering" 5/92 and the other Jay Baldwin on one side and Robert McFarland on the other side.
    - Agricuture (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Aids (Box 104, Folder 8)
      Includes cassette tape of interview with Don Turner, an aids survivor
    - Air pollution control (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Alaska (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Algae (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Allergies (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Alternative construction (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Alternative energy (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Angels (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Animal/human symbiosis (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Animal rights (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Architecture (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Aromatherapy (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Artists - art (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Astrology (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Astronomy (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Audio archive (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Audio literature (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Audio market (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Australian resources (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Automobiles (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Awards (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Ayurveda (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Betrayal (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Bicycles (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Birthing (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Black Athena (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Blind - organizations for (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Body image (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Bosnia (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Brain (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Breath (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Buddhism (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Burma (Box 105, Folder 24)